Edward @ Blair Morris.com

153 Palm Springs Way, Simpsonville SC 29681

919.801.6085

Web Design, Development, and Innovation

Web development is my main focus and passion. I strive to not only write the highest quality software possible, but to improve projects as a whole. Code quality tools, build automation, unit and E2E testing, and finally deployment, are vital to successful projects and satisfied clients. Above all, I put a heavy emphasis on a solid user experience, clean UI, and overall integration into personal branding.

Technology Experience

AngularJS/ReactJS/Backbone	Node.js / NPM	HTML5 (WebRTC, Websockets)
Twitter Bootstrap	CSS3/LESS/SCSS	Grunt/Gulp + Yeoman
BootstrapUI/AngularStrap	PostgreSQL/MongoDB	Express / Connect

And the usual: Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects), Microsoft Office Suite

Professional Experience

Under Armour, Inc. - Full Stack Web Engineer

August 2015 - Present

- Contributed to v6.5 rollout of new site updates prior to Black Friday 2015
- Developed replacement service and API layers of future version of http://www.UnderArmour.com

BMW Group - Front End Web Development Lead

March 2014 - August 2015

- Built CMS for eBook application used in all dealership training within the US.
- Designed CMS web application for dealership delivery processes and customer information.
- Designed and Built app store publishing system. Automated review process for apps to be published to the app stores.
- Transitioned all web projects to the MEAN stack (MongoDB, Express, Angular and Node.JS). Developed Yeoman generator with preconfigured NPM package, Grunt configurations and deployment setup.

Stanley Gibbons US, PLLC - UI/UX Developer

September 2013 - March 2014

- Built internal application replacing legacy stamp data entry system built on AngularJS/Bootstrap/MongoDB with a node.js backend. Incorporated LESS, Jade/EJS and Underscore.
- Worked with our backend team of php developers on a Symphony2 based eCommerce platform.
- Worked with UX professionals to plan styling and user interactions on front-end applications.

Credit Suisse Group – User Experience Engineer / Application Developer

July 2011 - September 2013

- Lead development on providing the firm's Executive Board an iOS application for viewing confidential client statistics.
- Developed a prototype mobile stock-trading platform, written in HTML5 with jQuery Mobile.
- Client and Internal facing application development

Standing Certifications

Certified Hardware Technician - IBM Corporation, Armonk, NY Professional Scrum Master I - Scrum.org

2010

2014

Education